http://miimadeinitaly.com/privacy-policy/

What does this privacy policy cover?
We take your privacy very seriously. This privacy policy governs and details the main privacy principles we apply to the data we collect through our services.
About our services
We specialize in a variety of services. Our aim is to deliver services based on your recent browsing behavior. With our service, you should receive personalized help that is more relevant for you than the standard one you would receive without us.
User Choices
If you do not want to receive ads displayed by us, on your current browser and browsers we have linked to your technical identifier you can disable the display of our ads here. If you only want to opt out from your current browser uncheck the opt-out box. You can also opt-out of all matched browsers and know more about user choices.
Our Technology
We collect information via technical cookies placed on your browser. Read more about our technology.
Data collection & use
We do not know who you are. We collect and use technical data relating to your browsing navigation to display personalized advertisements. Read more about data collection and use.
Our commitments and adherence
Our company is an early adopter to initiatives of greater transparency and control for users. Read more about transparency and control.
Data security and retention
The security of your information is fundamental to us. We have implemented industry-standard security measures, which include the use of firewalls and encryption. Read more about data security and retention. Please note that we may update or change this privacy policy. If we revise our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement, and to other places we deem appropriate, so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any we disclose it. If we make any material changes we will notify you by means of a notice on this site prior to the change becoming effective. Please click here for the latest version of the privacy policy.
E-mail:info@demolink.org
Please wait...
Subscribe to our newsletter
Enter your email address and name below to be the first to know.
Spread the love!
Share this product!
